[
    {
        "id": "1",
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct syntax to print a page using JavaScript?",
        "answer": {
            "ans1": "window.print();",
            "ans2": "browser.print();",
            "ans3": "navigator.print();",
            "ans4": "document.print();"
        },
        "right_answer": "window.print();"
    },
    {
        "id": "2",
        "question": "Which built-in method adds one or more elements to the end of an array and returns the new length of the array?",
        "answer": {
            "ans1": "last()",
            "ans2": "put()",
            "ans3": "push()"
        },
        "right_answer": "push()"
    },
    {
        "id": "3",
        "question": "Which of the following code creates an object?",
        "answer": {
            "ans1": "var book = Object();",
            "ans2": "var book = new Object();",
            "ans3": "var book = new OBJECT();",
            "ans4": "var book = new Book();"
        },
        "right_answer": "var book = new Object();"
    },
    {
        "id": "4",
        "question": "Which of the following function of Array object removes the last element from an array and returns that element?",
        "answer": {
            "ans1": "pop()",
            "ans2": "push()",
            "ans3": "join();",
            "ans4": "map();"
        },
        "right_answer": "pop()"
    },
    {
        "id": "5",
        "question": "Which of the following function of Array object removes the first element from an array and returns that element?",
        "answer": {
            "ans1": "reverse()",
            "ans2": "shift()",
            "ans3": "slice();",
            "ans4": "some();"
        },
        "right_answer": "shift()"
    },
    {
        "id": "6",
        "question": "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
        "answer": {
            "ans1": "var",
            "ans2": "let",
            "ans3": "const",
            "ans4": "All answer is correct"
        },
        "right_answer": "All answer is correct"
    },
    {
        "id": "7",
        "question": "When an operatorâ€™s value is NULL, the typeof returned by the unary operator is:",
        "answer": {
            "ans1": "Boolean",
            "ans2": "Undefined",
            "ans3": "Object",
            "ans4": "Integer"
        },
        "right_answer": "Object"
    },
    {
        "id": "8",
        "question": "Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in Javascript?",
        "answer": {
            "ans1": "stringify()",
            "ans2": "parse()",
            "ans3": "convert()",
            "ans4": "None of them"
        },
        "right_answer": "stringify()"
    },
    {
        "id": "9",
        "question": "Which of the following are closures in Javascript?",
        "answer": {
            "ans1": "Variables",
            "ans2": "Functions",
            "ans3": "Objects",
            "ans4": "All answer is correct"
        },
        "right_answer": "All answer is correct"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a Javascript framework?",
        "answer": {
            "ans1": "Node",
            "ans2": "Vue",
            "ans3": "Cassandra"
        },
        "right_answer": "Cassandra"
    }
]